//Array of question no., question, options and answers
let questions = [
    {
        num: 1,
        question: "A strawberry is not technically a berry. What is it?",
        answer: "An accessory fruit",
        options:[
                "An accessory fruit",
                "A hybrid vegetable",
                "A cruciferous vegetable",
                "Trick question- It's a berry"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 2,
        question: "In which city was the first Olympic games held?",
        answer: "Athens",
        options:[
                "Los Angeles",
                "Rome",
                "Olympia",
                "Athens"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 3,
        question: "To where was the first marathon run historically?",
        answer: "Athens",
        options:[
                "Athens",
                "Boston",
                "Sparta",
                "Argos"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 4,
        question: "Look at the series: 7,10,8,11,9,12,_ .What number should come next?",
        answer: "10",
        options:[
                "7",
                "10",
                "12",
                "13"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 5,
        question: "Which movie won the best picture award at the 95th annual Academy Award?",
        answer: "Everything Everywhere All at Once",
        options:[
                "Angel Negro",
                "The King's speech",
                "Everything Everywhere All at Once",
                "The Whale",
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 6,
        question: "Select the option which is different from the other three options.",
        answer: "Dust-Vacuum cleaner",
        options:[
                "Petrol-Car",
                "Ink-pen",
                "Electric-fan",
                "Dust-Vacuum cleaner"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 7,
        question: "In which year was the first Academy Award given?",
        answer: "1929",
        options:[
                "1929",
                "1954",
                "1977",
                "1988"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 8,
        question: "In terms of land area, what is the smallest capital city in the world?",
        answer: "Vatican City",
        options:[
                "Ankara",
                "Vatican City",
                "Cardiff",
                "Nuuk"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 9,
        question: "Whose assassination is considered to be one of the reason to trigger world war I?",
        answer: "Arcduke Franz Ferdinand",
        options:[
                "Reinhard heydrich",
                "Jean Jaur√®s",
                "Arcduke Franz Ferdinand",
                "Charlotte Corday"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 10,
        question: "What Netflix show had the most streaming views in 2021?",
        answer: "Squid Game",
        options:[
                "Arcane",
                "Squid Game",
                "Stranger Things",
                "Money Heist",
        ]
    }
]